Guide to the General Counsel, Yale University, Records
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
General counsel, Yale University, records
1952-2001
RU 128
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
293.0
(282 containers)
The records consist of correspondence, litigation files,research files, subject files, reports, court transcripts, and printed matterdetailing the work of the general counsel's office at Yale University.
Yale University. Office of the General Counsel
General note
Forms part of Yale Record Group 2-C (YRG2-C), Records documenting Yale legal affairs.
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the records is restricted to the office of origin only.
Scope and Contents
Therecords consist of correspondence, litigation files, research files, subject files, reports, court transcripts, and printed matter detailing the work of the general counsel's office at Yale University.
Arrangement
The records are arranged by accession.
Actions and defenses; Yale University. Office of the General Counsel; Yale University -- Administration
- Records for Greenburg v.Yale-New Haven Hospital, circa 1952-1983; Accession 1983-A-088
  Conditions Governing Access
  Restricted to office of origin only.
- Records and litigation files, 1975-1983; Accession 1983-A-089
- Litigation and subject files, 1976-1983; Accession 1984-A-056 (Box 1–22)
- Records for IRS v.Yale, circa 1974-1982; Accession 1986-A-060
  Restrictedto office of origin only.
- Chronological files of Linda Lorimer, 1978-1984; Accession 1986-A-096
- Litigation and chronological files, 1976-1986; Accession 1987-A-022
- Litigation files, 1972-1985; Accession 1987-A-038
- Records, circa 1963-1986; Accession 1987-A-097
- Litigation, subject, and chronological files, circa 1969-1987; Accession 1990-A-151 (Box 1–25)
  Scope and Contents
  No online inventory available. Paper inventory available in repository.
- Records, circa 1972-1987; Accession 1991-A-059 (Box 1–15)
- Records, 1976-1988; Accession 1991-A-107
  Restricted to office of originonly.
- Records, circa1980-1989; Accession 1992-A-022 (Box 1–8)
- Litigation, discrimination and personnel complaint records, 1981-1990; Accession 1994-A-075
- Student loan, individual donor, JEC chrons, KRM chrons, CC chrons, DKR chrons, litigation and other subject files, 1977-1990; Accession 1996-A-012 (Box 1–22)
- Litigation records, undated; Accession 1996-A-057
- Donor, litigation, and chronological files, 1982-1995; Accession 1997-A-081
- Chronological files of the general counsel's office, 1988-1996; Accession 2005-A-102
- Case files of the general counsel's office, 1987-1997; Accession 2005-A-103
- Litigation and subject files, 1987-2001; 1997-2001; Accession 2015-A-047
  Related Materials
  University Tribunal, Yale University, Records (RU 1115) contains the records of Sidney Altman as Chair of the University Tribunal from 1997-2001.
  Restricted to Office of Origin only